https://www.massage-chair-relief.com/privacy

Our Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us.We want to make your experience on the internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the internet’s vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how Massage Chair Relief® collects information from all end users of Massage Chair Relief® ' internet services (the "Services") — those who access some of our Services but do not make a purchase ("Visitors") as well as those who make a purchase ("Customers") — what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Customers have concerning the collection and use of such information. Massage Chair Relief® requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.IntroductionMassage Chair Relief® collects information from customers who make a purchase on our website. Massage Chair Relief® also collects information from Visitors that request information from our site. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.Data SecurityThe information you provide—including credit card information—is secured using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. We use this SSL technology to prevent such information from being intercepted and read as it is transmitted over the Internet. The encrypted data goes to a secure site where your information is stored on restricted-access computers located at restricted-access sites. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.Responses to Email InquiriesWhen Visitors or Customers send email inquiries to Massage Chair Relief®, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Massage Chair Relief® does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party."Cookies" and Massage Chair Relief® Uses ThemA "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. Massage Chair Relief® may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. If you are a Customer, we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit non- Massage Chair Relief® web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies.Special CasesIt is the policy of Massage Chair Relief® not to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Customers in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to prohibit such unrelated uses. However, Massage Chair Relief® may disclose personal information about Visitors or Customers, if we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to operate the Services properly or to protect Massage Chair Relief®.Massage Chair Relief®'s Commitment to Children's PrivacyProtecting children’s privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws.Revisions to This PolicyMassage Chair Relief® reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted here and will only apply to information collected after any such change.Where to Direct Questions About this Privacy PolicyMassage Chair Relief®2248 W. 5400 S.Taylorsville, UT 84129Phone toll free 888-259-5380Or E-mail us
